[
    {
        "text": "John Doe lives in New York City and his phone number is 123-456-7890.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 8, "PERSON"],
            [22, 34, "GPE"],
            [44, 58, "PHONE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Apple Inc. announced the launch of their new product in San Francisco on January 10, 2025.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 10, "ORG"],
            [57, 70, "GPE"],
            [74, 88, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Smith works at Microsoft and lives in Seattle.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 10, "PERSON"],
            [22, 31, "ORG"],
            [42, 49, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Barack Obama was born on August 4, 1961, in Honolulu.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 12, "PERSON"],
            [20, 32, "DATE"],
            [36, 44, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The event will take place at the White House, Washington on July 4th.",
        "entities": [
            [32, 43, "LOCATION"],
            [45, 58, "GPE"],
            [63, 74, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Elon Musk, CEO of SpaceX, is often seen in California.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 10, "PERSON"],
            [12, 16, "ORG"],
            [28, 37, "PERSON"],
            [51, 60, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My phone number is 555-123-4567. Call me anytime.",
        "entities": [
            [18, 32, "PHONE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I visited Tokyo, Japan last week.",
        "entities": [
            [9, 14, "GPE"],
            [16, 21, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "On the 15th of September 2023, Microsoft made a major acquisition.",
        "entities": [
            [3, 15, "DATE"],
            [17, 26, "ORG"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rihanna's latest album, Anti, was released in 2016.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 7, "PERSON"],
            [28, 32, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The Great Wall of China is a popular tourist destination.",
        "entities": [
            [4, 21, "LOCATION"],
            [27, 41, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Albert Einstein was a theoretical physicist born in Ulm, Germany.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 14, "PERSON"],
            [43, 47, "GPE"],
            [49, 56, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Google's headquarters are located in Mountain View, California.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 6, "ORG"],
            [39, 56, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The concert is on Friday, December 10th at Madison Square Garden in New York.",
        "entities": [
            [28, 44, "DATE"],
            [48, 70, "LOCATION"],
            [74, 82, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mark Zuckerberg announced the Facebook rebrand to Meta on October 28, 2021.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 13, "PERSON"],
            [45, 51, "ORG"],
            [55, 74, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The United Nations was established on 24th October 1945.",
        "entities": [
            [4, 19, "ORG"],
            [40, 59, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "James Cameron, the director of Titanic, was born in Kapuskasing, Ontario.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 12, "PERSON"],
            [26, 33, "ORG"],
            [55, 67, "GPE"],
            [69, 76, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The COVID-19 pandemic started in 2019 and affected many countries, including Italy and Spain.",
        "entities": [
            [4, 11, "MISC"],
            [26, 30, "DATE"],
            [58, 63, "GPE"],
            [68, 73, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tesla's Model S was released in 2012.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 5, "ORG"],
            [13, 19, "MISC"],
            [31, 35, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jennifer Lawrence starred in The Hunger Games and was born in Louisville, Kentucky.",
        "entities": [
            [0, 17, "PERSON"],
            [46, 63, "ORG"],
            [67, 76, "GPE"],
            [78, 86, "GPE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The birth of the new child is scheduled for July 15, 2025.",
        "entities": [
            [49, 61, "DATE"]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The Grand Canyon is one of the seven natural wonders of the world.",
        "entities": [
            [4, 18, "LOCATION"]
        ]
    }
]
